movified.com 2017-08-29

# Movified | Privacy Policy

**Movified Privacy Notice**

**Last Updated, December 9, 2015**

Thank you for using Movified. This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to your use of Movified's website, products, app, and services (together, the "Services"). The Policy is intended to inform you about how we collect and use information so you can make an informed decision about using the Services. Please read it carefully before using the Services or submitting any information to us. If you do not agree to any part of this Policy, then you should stop accessing the Services.

**What Personal Information About Users Does Movified Gather?**

The information we learn from users helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at Movified. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information You Give Us** : We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future browsing for you, improving our site, and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information** : We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses Movified or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Movified on other websites.

**E-mail Communications** : To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Movified if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users.

**Mobile** : When you access our website from your mobile, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services.

**Information from other Sources** : We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide personalized features and browsing preferences.

We use technologies to measure the effectiveness of certain site features and to conduct research and analysis. We also allow third parties to conduct research and analysis on our website, but we do not provide personal information to such third parties.

**Movified does not sell information to Third Parties**

Information about our users is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others.

**Agents** : We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from user lists, analysing data, and providing marketing assistance. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Promotional Offers** : Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Movified users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and e-mail address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please use our website to adjust your preferences.

**Protection of Movified and Others** : We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply ourConditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Movified, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

**With Your Consent** : Other than as set out above, you will always receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**Third-Party Advertisers**

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites.

These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens.

They may also use technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

**Security of my information**

If you use our subscription service, we work to protect the security of your subscription information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Please sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Options**

You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of personalized Movified features.

You can add or update certain information, such as your e-mail address. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please use our Settings page to adjust your preferences. (If you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of Movified, and it is your responsibility to review such notices for changes.)

**Children**

By using Movified Services, you represent that you have either reached the age of "majority" where you live or have valid parent or legal guardian consent to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not know whether you have reached the age of majority where you live, or do not understand this section, please ask your parent or legal guardian for help before you create a Movified account. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a minor that creates a Movified account, you accept this policy on minor’s behalf and are responsible for all use of the Movified account or Services, whether the minor’s account is now open or created later.

Please note that Movified Services are not intended for users who have not reached the age of majority. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from users or market to or solicit information from anyone who has not reached the age of majority. If we become aware that a person submitting personal information has not reached the age of majority, we will delete the account and any related information as soon as possible. If you believe we might have any information from or about a user,who has not reached the age of majority, please contact us at:

contact@movified.com

**Dispute Resolution, Notices and Revisions**

If you choose to visit Movified, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of India.

If you have any concern about privacy at Movified, please contact us at:

contact@movified.com

Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
